In December I made a video about a 4mm silicone catsuit and there were so so many questions
which I'm going to address today wearing a new 4mm silicone catsuit this time in pink.
So I also know that a lot of you bought the catsuit and are quite happy with it so thank
Thank you for that, I appreciate that apparently my video was a good one and inspired you to
get a silicone catsuit.
But as I said, under the YouTube video, under the Instagram Reel, so many questions and
let's do a FAQ about this silicone catsuit from OANYA.
But first let's admire this one for a second because I took the time and it took me a while
to get into it.
I'm probably going to show you later how I get out of it
So that's going to be interesting and also one of the main questions
But let's start with the first one question number one was how does it feel also in comparison to latex?
So how does it feel?
Do you know these?
baking forms
They're also made from silicon and they basically do feel
the same so like really thick really soft I would say that the catsuit feels even softer
if you don't know how these feel next time at the supermarket just go to the baking area and
touch one of these compared to latex it feels as I said softer but they're also no seams so it's
also still smoother than latex for a seamless look and it's a bit heavier than latex because
this is four millimeter thickness so around about four kilogram. The second question was how do you
go to the toilet with that because there is no crotch zipper and it's as easy as that. I don't.
I use my brain and before I put it on I'll go to the toilet. I don't drink like five liters of water
before I put it on I don't eat something from which I know I have to go to the loo immediately
so yeah just do that before put it on and then get out of it again if you're done there are a ton of
other situations where people just can't go to the toilet as they please think about football
players during a match or singers or band members during a concert they can't just run off and say
I have to go to the loo. A lot of you said like what if there's an emergency bathroom break
And I'm like, I don't know if it's just me, but I don't have emergency bathroom breaks
Is this guy thing?
But if you really really really have to go to the toilet while you're wearing the catsuit you can
Simply get out of it and undress and I'm going to show you that at the end of the video
How to dress it was the next question and as this is a neck entry catsuit, which is really really stretchy
you kind of start at the feet and pull it up I have a video with the black cat
suit in which I show how to dress and you also need water-based lubricant
pretty important water-based lubricant and if you want to shine it afterwards
you should use the product specially made for this and not just some kind of
latex shine. By the way Roania and Smitherson are sister companies so they
They might offer slightly different products but I have a discount code for both of them
and you should just check out their webshops and see what you can find there.
Then there was the assumption that I sweat a lot while wearing this and I have to say
I don't or rather it depends. It depends on the room or the outside temperature because this does
not insulate like latex so if it's cold I will freeze, if it's hot I will sweat. Does it smell
or how does it smell? I think it smells a bit chemical when you are pack it but if you expose
it to fresh air then the smell will vanish. As for the fit this is a one size product
and I'm on the lower range of the recommended sizing. This is supposed to fit people from 60
to 100 kilogram as a reference I'm 173 centimeters tall I think it barely fits me it's a bit too loose
at some points and a bit too long especially when I sit down but it is super super super stretchy
and everyone basically can squeeze into it with a lot of lube. Regarding the comfort
it is for kilogram yes but I don't think you kind of feel that of course after
a while you realize oh it's a bit heavy on my shoulders but it's really really
comfortable since it's super stretchy it's like I can move a lot around I can
lift my arms I can lift my legs due to stretchiness it is super comfy how long
does the shipping take was another question and I have to say it depends on production capacity
so you better should ask Roanje or Smitherson after you placed your order they can help you out
you've maybe already seen the mask here I can show it to you a bit closer this is a man's
one size mask and as you can already see it's way too loose here on the styrofoam head
so I suggested for heads around 60 centimeter circumference and of course it is way way way
too big for me which is one reason why I'm not wearing it but there are a few other reasons why
I'm not wearing masks on my channel for one I would totally ruin my makeup and my hair and as
for a day like today I'm recording multiple videos so it would be not really clever to ruin my makeup
in the middle and have to reapply it. On top of that I don't never wear masks. I did wear a mask
in a Sentai video but this is not a fetish channel. It is a channel about alternative fashion and
kinky stuff and it's a bit of entertainment. It's a bit of information. So if you just want to see
stupid fetish content you have to look for that elsewhere. But not here. There is like a boundary
I set myself and that's just simply what I like to do or don't. However I will place a spoiler
here. There is going to be an upcoming video with Ruan Yao in which I will wear a mask although a
really really different kind of mask so keep your eyes open for that. What if there is a tear in
your silicone catsuit or mask? You can fix that yourself using Silpoxie and you will find an
instruction for that on the FAQ page on the submission homepage but you can also send it
to the company and they will fix it for you just ask them someone or rather a few persons ask how
long can you wear such a catsuit easy however long you feel like wearing it because that the skin has
to breathe is an urban myth you breathe through your mouth and your nose your skin doesn't really
care and again it is really really really stretchy like this stretchy so you should be
able to get into it and out of it and feel comfortable it does not feel like it's too
restricting I'm not claustrophobic when I'm wearing it although I don't have that problem
at all anyway so yeah just however you feel like just try it out yourself and
now to everyone who asked and there were quite a few people who asked that what
if you have to fart use your brain I'm not going to answer it what's wrong with
you guys all right I hope I answered all of your questions if you have further
questions write them down in the comments if I already answered it I'll
was just right have a look at the video again anyway I hope you like this color
it is quite pink I think it's pretty cute you can actually see that it's a
bit see-through so I'm wearing a bodysuit underneath with some darker
parts and you can see them it's not totally see-through and there are
different colors available so I already tried the black one which you can see
here also for the dressing part again but they are also red and blue and
transparent and skin as colors available so I think this is the newest one or one
of the new ones and I love how it fits I also love which I have to say again that
it's pre-molded so it makes a great booty because the butt cheeks are
actually pre-molded so to say yeah so they're not flat they're not pushing my booty down
but rather enhancing it and yeah it looks nice I promised you earlier for the emergency bathroom
breaks I will show you now how to get out of it at least I try I hope it works it should be working
I put a lot of water-based lubricant inside and I'm also used to get out of my latex neck entry
catsuits so wish me luck
Not gonna lie, it is easier if you have help from someone, especially with the shoulders.
But you see, once I'm done with shoulders, it's pretty fast.
I'm sweating.
This sounds...
And yeah, a lot of lube does help a lot.
If you're really struggling to get under the shower, turn on the water and use the water
to get out of it.
Alright, that was...
I'm out of breath.
That was today's video.
I hope you enjoyed it and this is my final look.
Leave a thumbs up, check out the description text I linked, the shop I wrote down my description,
my description, my discount code.
And leave a comment and a thumbs up.
I will see you in the next video, thanks for sticking around, bye.